Ajay's
student looked down, the heroine Devendra
Kumar Gupta played the role and
in these two months, by joining the Delhi Police,
10,000 migrant labour families are
given ration for a month, 620 babies are
provided milk during the pendant is
ICICI Lombard Prince, this is the
story of long gown, hero due
Devendra Kumar, the work we are doing on the ground is
very important for these families, all of you are also doing a
very good job in this, but now Tay
Ladli Foundation has
given ration for one month to 10,000 such families and in the same way,
we want to keep working and
want to work with a smile so that
more smiles can come on people's faces.
[Music]